export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How often do you find yourself experiencing anxiety in daily situations?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely",
        "Occasionally",
        "Frequently",
        "Almost always"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you tend to express your anxiety outwardly or keep it to yourself?",
      "options": [
        "Express outwardly",
        "Keep to myself",
        "Varies depending on the situation",
        "I don't experience anxiety"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Keep to myself"
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers your anxiety the most?",
      "options": [
        "Uncertainty",
        "Social situations",
        "Performance expectations",
        "Other (please specify)"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Uncertainty"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you describe the intensity of your anxiety when it occurs?",
      "options": [
        "Mild",
        "Moderate",
        "Severe",
        "Extreme"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Mild"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you actively seek methods to manage and control your anxiety?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, regularly",
        "Sometimes",
        "Rarely",
        "No, not at all"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Yes, regularly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your anxiety behavior?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, frequently",
        "Occasionally",
        "Rarely",
        "No, never"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Occasionally"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel regret or guilt after experiencing anxiety?",
      "options": [
        "Always",
        "Sometimes",
        "Rarely",
        "Never"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Sometimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or counseling for anxiety-related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes",
        "Considering it",
        "No, not yet",
        "No, and I don't plan to"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you rate the impact of anxiety on your relationships and daily life?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact",
        "Moderate impact",
        "High impact",
        "Very high impact"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Moderate impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing anxiety is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree",
        "Agree",
        "Neutral",
        "Disagree"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    }
  ]
}
